module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is ChelsB\'s middle name?', 
    a: 'Taylor',
    b: 'Danger',
    c: 'Anita',
    d: 'Rebecca',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which one of these people has shot ChelsB with a paintball gun?', 
    a: 'Shaun White\'s mom',
    b: 'Bass player from Foster the People',
    c: 'Chuck Norris\' Stunt double',
    d: 'Nick Baldoni',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many slack emojis has ChelsB created?', 
    a: '31',
    b: '72',
    c: '46',
    d: '53',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where has ChelsB not lived?', 
    a: 'Wisconsin',
    b: 'Minnesota',
    c: 'Iowa',
    d: 'Illinois',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What sport(s) did ChelsB play growing up?', 
    a: 'Basketball',
    b: 'Track & Field',
    c: 'Soccer',
    d: 'all of the above',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How old is ChelsB?', 
    a: '25',
    b: '26',
    c: '27',
    d: '28',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which national health concern first started in ChelsB\'s hometown of Hamilton, NJ?', 
    a: 'Anthrax',
    b: 'Bird Flu',
    c: 'Swine Flu',
    d: 'Justin Bieber',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'ChelsB\'s dog\'s name is Wisco - which is short for what?', 
    a: 'Whiskey',
    b: 'Whiskers',
    c: 'Nothing',
    d: 'Wisconsin',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'ChelsB has eaten fruit from Bill Murray\'s orchard. What kind of fruit was it?', 
    a: 'Tangleo',
    b: 'Pomelo',
    c: 'Lime-elo',
    d: 'Apple',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
  question: 'Which one of these people has ChelsB seen do a backflip?', 
  a: 'Shaun White\'s mom',
  b: 'Bass player from Foster the People',
  c: 'Chuck Norris\' Stunt double',
  d: 'Nick Baldoni',
  answer: 'c'
  },
];